Anywhere you are, distance is not a barrier.
Viewers, you are called to behold the spiritual entities which cause crisis in your lives.
You and Prophet T.B. Joshua together, in the name of Jesus, can stop satan
killing, stealing and destroying your life.
Touch the screen, right now. Engage with God!
Viewers all over the world, where can you go from His presence?
Whatever challenges, whatever situation you are passing through,
I knew you will be under the influence of this telecast at this time.
Right now, listen.
I have been commissioned to rescue you.
Be rescued!
Your health, be rescued!
Your marital life, be rescued!
Your finances, be rescued!
Your business, be rescued!
Your career, be rescued!
Be rescued!
Your future, be rescued!
In the name of Jesus!
We leave you under the influence of the Holy Spirit and pray to meet you there again.
Allow you heart to be deeply engaged with God as you send your testimony.
RV: Mel Flowers 16/04/2019